If I were to add a few things to that
book, one of them would be the dangers
of valuing your time very highly and
making that an immovable pillar of your
life. What I mean by that is on one
level, to a certain degree, and the dose
makes the poison. I think that's
Paracelsus, but you can apply it here,
which is learning to value your time is
a valuable skill. It allows you to
learn, especially in the early stages,
what makes sense to delegate and what
does not. What is worth doing versus
what is not worth doing. And so, you
start to develop the ability to then
later do things like 80/20 analysis and
automation and all of the things that
are in that book. However, if you land
on some type of number, whether it's
ill-defined or very precisely defined
for what you are worth, what your time
is worth per hour, you can end up
feeling the agony of wasting time
anytime a minute is sacrificed doing
something that you don't think is
high-leverage. And that ends up being a
very painful way to go through life.